Privacy Policy
==============

We take your privacy very seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.

**Privacy Policy**  
We respect and protect the privacy of the individuals that use our website. Individually identifiable information about you is **NOT** disclosed to any third party as explained in this privacy policy ("Privacy Policy").

**What information do we collect?**  
We do **NOT** collect any individually identifiable information about you (such as your name, email address, ip address, etc.) except when you specifically and knowingly provide such information in the form of an email.

**Cookies**  
When you use our website no cookies are used by default. If you make changes to any setting then cookies are used to store those changes. None of the cookies have user identifiable information. None of the cookies track you.

**With whom do we share information?**  
We will **NOT** share individually identifiable information about you with any advertisers, business partners, sponsors, and other third parties. We may disclose or share non-personal or anonymous or aggregated information with third parties, such as usage statistics of our Services or IP addresses. Aggregated non-personally identifiable information is information recorded about users and collected into groups so that it no longer reflects or references an individually identifiable user.

**Links to other websites**  
The sites displayed as search results or linked to by our website are developed by people over whom we exercise no control. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information, we do not.

**Are we adware, spyware or malware?**  
Absolutely not! We do **NOT**; monitor, collect data or 'spy' on our customers. We are incapable of tracking your overall web use or deciphering anything on your hard drive. We do **NOT** display pop-up ads or any type of advertising except for paid search results. All server logs are disabled. We DO NOT distribute any software programs at all (including internet browsers or toolbars).

**How do we make any money, if you offer it for free?**  
We share revenue from sponsored search results.

**Changes to this privacy policy**  
This Privacy Policy may change from time to time. You are responsible for periodically reviewing this Privacy Policy for any applicable changes.

**Questions and/or Suggestions**  
If you have questions and/or suggestions, please [Contact Us](https://www.alltheinternet.com/?area=contactus)
